<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title><![CDATA[everything will be AMAZING]]></title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-03-29T06:59:40.730Z</updated>
  <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[lindsey]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[lindsey@clevergirl.me]]></email>
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://zespia.tw/hexo/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[What Am I Doing]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/28/What-Am-I-Doing/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/28/What-Am-I-Doing/</id>
    <published>2016-03-29T06:27:20.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-03-29T06:53:55.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’m really not sure what I’m trying to do here. I’ll style it sooner or later, but I need to start writing online again and I need it to be just my own. Leaena.com needed to become my engineering persona. I want this to be more freeform. I want to post cat pictures and writing snippets and knitting and and and…</p>
<h5 id="So_goal_time:">So goal time:</h5>
<blockquote>
<p>I will write every day. At least 100 words. I can say as much or as little as I want. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Maybe I’ll ist the songs I’ve listened to or talk about the weirdest link I clicked on today.</p>
<p>My fun fact today is that I learned what the hell a <a href="https://developers.google.com/protocol-buffers/" target="_blank" rel="external">Proto Buffer</a> actually is. I haven’t backend engineered in a long time. And here I said this didn’t need to be about engineering…</p>
<p>I think tomorrow I will probably talk about/test out a bunch of different markdown editors. This is <a href="http://dillinger.io/" target="_blank" rel="external">Dillinger</a> and it’s decent but I’m not sure if I want a web based solution or not. I guess it would be pretty hip of me.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>I’m really not sure what I’m trying to do here. I’ll style it sooner or later, but I need to start writing online again and I need it to ]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
