<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title><![CDATA[everything will be AMAZING]]></title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-04-06T06:50:46.460Z</updated>
  <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[lindsey]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[lindsey@clevergirl.me]]></email>
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://zespia.tw/hexo/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Give Up the Funk]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/04/05/give-up-the-funk/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/04/05/give-up-the-funk/</id>
    <published>2016-04-06T06:21:22.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-04-06T06:50:36.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’m in a bit of a funk. To be honest, I’ve been in one for quite awhile, but it’s finally starting to get to me.</p>
<p>The problem is, I don’t really do anything anymore. I go to work, I go home, I watch tv, I go to bed. I go to work, I go home, I go to the grocery store, I go to bed. Weekends aren’t much better. I wake up late, do a couple of chores (vacuum, laundry, whatever) and then I laze around on the internet or reading or petting cats.</p>
<p>I really need to <strong>do</strong> something. I don’t know what to do. Exercise sounds like a decent option but I’m really self concious about going to the gym by myself. I wouldn’t mind taking a class but most of those seem to be geared toward housewives who can make a 11am class no problem (no shade to the housewives, I just generally have to be at work around then).</p>
<p>I could go join something about a hobby of mine, but most of my hobbies lend themselves to solo pursuits or involve video games and I have friends all over the world who are willing to play video games with me.</p>
<p>I need to find something though because this funk is just compounding with everything. Leaving me burnt out and tired and making it even harder to get out of this funk.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>I’m in a bit of a funk. To be honest, I’ve been in one for quite awhile, but it’s finally starting to get to me.</p>
<p>The problem is, I]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Picture Is Worth a Thousand Words]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/04/03/picture-is-worth-a-thousand-words/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/04/03/picture-is-worth-a-thousand-words/</id>
    <published>2016-04-04T03:29:37.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-04-04T03:34:45.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Just as I was starting to say nice things about the Typora markdown editor it goes and eats part of my markdown file. So since I said I was going to post at least 100 words a day, have a picture instead.</p>
<p><img src="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/s/qhgxabp9j7b7qop/2016-03-11%2019.25.53.jpg" alt=""></p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>Just as I was starting to say nice things about the Typora markdown editor it goes and eats part of my markdown file. So since I said I w]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Weirdness of the Week]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/04/02/weirdness-of-the-week/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/04/02/weirdness-of-the-week/</id>
    <published>2016-04-03T05:04:40.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-04-03T20:48:01.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>Editor’s note: Because I run this show I’m setting the time for this back to Saturday. I started a post on time but I was legit not home long enough to write real words yesterday.</em></p>
<p>I’ve discovered 3D movies are not for me. To be fair, I’ve discovered this before. In college some friends and I had the ridiculous idea of watching the truly awful Journey to the Center of the Earth with Brendan Fraser. To this day I mourn Brendan Fraser’s acting career.</p>
<p>At the time we sat around their flatscreen that they probably paid way too much for because this was ten years ago and you didn’t see me and my roommate buying a flatscreen. Walmart TV all the way for us. We even had the old school 3D glasses, cardboard with a red eye and a blue eye that you had to get creative to wear while still keeping your glasses on.</p>
<p>So we were watching just fine. 3D <strong>always</strong> then, and often now, was about the gimmick. So most of the scene was flat and every once in awhile some stupid bird would fly at your face. But the scene that got me, the scene where I  screamed out loud and couldn’t even anymore, was a panorama shot where literally a plant leaf popped into view and scared the crap out of me.</p>
<p>I have never lived that moment down. I probably don’t deserve to ever live that moment down.</p>
<p>I watched Zootopia yesterday in 3D. The 3D was less gimmicky so it didn’t scare the crap out of me. But 10 years have made me older. When I walked out of the theater this time, I just had a giant headache.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p><em>Editor’s note: Because I run this show I’m setting the time for this back to Saturday. I started a post on time but I was legit not h]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Orphaned]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/04/01/orphaned/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/04/01/orphaned/</id>
    <published>2016-04-02T02:34:34.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-04-02T04:49:49.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A bit of fiction because my life is too boring today to talk about the real world:</p>
<p>Melanie’s restlessness was an alive thing. It skittered away from her, ruffling the other children in the small classroom. Causing a younger girl to yawn audibly while their class aid tried to gain control.</p>
<p>The aid was new, and it said a lot for turnover that Melanie even noticed. Two weeks. She had the ink marks under her sleeve to prove it. Three was the longest she’d ever gone, but two was still unbearable.</p>
<p>The learning hour ended with no real fanfare. The aid had never gained control and the built up squirming of the children spilled out to the rest of the building. </p>
<p>Melanie nearly vibrated as she made her way to the common area. The flow of children around her like stream. She wouldn’t let herself get caught up in it. She wasn’t excited that the school day was over. It was just another day to scratch off. Her mother was a much better teacher anyway.</p>
<p>There weren’t enough tables  in the room for her to sit by herself so she instead sat at a crowded table. Ignoring the initial stares of the children, she tucked her chin to her chest.</p>
<p>Quickly the others ignored her. Everyone except for Amanda who kept her eyes narrowed on the interloper to her table.</p>
<p>“So are your parents in jail or did they just hate you?” Amanda asked. Still staring at Melanie, she wore a smirk of triumph at her cruel question.</p>
<p>The table went silent. One boy who’s father was in jail went white. Melanie for her part, welcomed the distraction. And besides, she loved talking about her mother.</p>
<p>“My mom needed to keep me safe,” Melanie said, meeting Amanda’s eyes.</p>
<p>“So she’s a drug addict then. Thought so.”</p>
<p>“My mom’s a secret agent,” Melanie said, with a proud smile. “It’s safer if no one knows where I am while she works.”</p>
<p>A couple of the kids laughed quietly, from the tension and the strange answer.</p>
<p>“Is that what she told you before she left you here? That’s pathetic. She lied to you like that?”</p>
<p>“She didn’t lie,” Melanie retorted. She almost loved this part. They never believed. Sometimes after she left she imagined what the children’s faces must look like. When they realized she wasn’t lying.</p>
<p>At only 12, Melanie had been on a whirlwind tour of a whole variety of orphanages. None of them had been as bad as some of the awful books her mom had read to her about orphanages.</p>
<p>Once Melanie had told her she was almost disappointed. She thought if she went to a bad orphanage she’d at least have a story to share with her mom. Her mother told wonderful stories, of the strange prince she’d protected somewhere in Asia to the daring escape she’d had to make when her cover was blown in South America.</p>
<p>When Melanie told her she wished she had stories to tell, she kissed the top of her head absentmindedly. “I have enough stories for the both of us. I’d rather keep you safe.”</p>
<p>And so it was two days later, in the quiet of dawn that Melanie’s mother took her hand and walked her out of the latest orphanage. In a small act of defiance, Melanie tugged a braid of Amanda’s hair as they passed by her cot and slipped out of the building before the rest of the world woke up to discover her gone.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>A bit of fiction because my life is too boring today to talk about the real world:</p>
<p>Melanie’s restlessness was an alive thing. It s]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Words to Soothe the Savage Beast]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/31/words-to-soothe-the-savage-beast/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/31/words-to-soothe-the-savage-beast/</id>
    <published>2016-04-01T02:47:20.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-04-01T04:50:55.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’ve been taking some time lately to read more books. I have a soft spot especially for Young Adult fiction. I just never grew up I guess. I’ve also always felt that Young Adult books can be more fanciful and expect the readers to suspend disbelief more while still having amazing plot and characters. What it means is that I get to spend time in so many different world.</p>
<p>My routine lately leaves less time for reading, but I’ve made a point to read as much as I can on my 20 minute train ride to and from the city for work. I stick my headphones in and unless I have the perfect playlist for the mood the book gives me (Harry Potter will always be Astrolounge by Smash Mouth for example) I’ll just use that as earplugs to keep me in the book world.</p>
<p>Lately I’ve been reading a lot of delicious scary novels. Books like <a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/18748653-daughters-unto-devils" target="_blank" rel="external">Daughters Unto Devils</a> that are melancoly and don’t always turn out the way you’d hoped. They’re fun but I needed something a little more fanciful. So I dug through my “To Read” list on Goodreads and decided it was high time I started reading the first book I every added to that list.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/10763598-daughter-of-smoke-bone" target="_blank" rel="external">Daughter of Smoke and Bone</a> was… consuming. It was everything I was looking for in a book and brought me back to my childhood of falling in love with the world and heroine likes the ones set before me in Tamora Pierce’s <a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/492490.The_Song_of_the_Lioness_Quartet" target="_blank" rel="external">The Song of the Lioness Quartet</a> and Patricia C Wrede’s <a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/86238.The_Enchanted_Forest_Chronicles" target="_blank" rel="external">Enchanted Forest Chronicles</a>.</p>
<p>I can still remember the day I discovered that the single book I’d read over and over and over and over again, <a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/150739.Dealing_with_Dragons" target="_blank" rel="external">Dealing with Dragons</a> was actually a SERIES. I read and read and read and never looked back.</p>
<p>This is what Daughter of Smoke and Bone does to me. It makes me want to read. To devour it all and live and breathe the world so I can be <em>Elsewhere</em> for a time. It also makes me want to re-read my favorite two series (well basically everything in Tamora Pierce’s world not just the Lioness series) all over again.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>I’ve been taking some time lately to read more books. I have a soft spot especially for Young Adult fiction. I just never grew up I guess]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Cat Trills and Shadowboxing]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/30/cat-trills-and-shadowboxing/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/30/cat-trills-and-shadowboxing/</id>
    <published>2016-03-31T04:24:35.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-04-01T04:21:54.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I don’t know what I’m doing. I think I might be burnt out but I’m not sure how to tell anymore. I just feel like I’ve stopped processing basically everything around me. I’m running on autopilot. Work, home, work, home.</p>
<p>This will make me sound like even more of a crazy cat lady than was previously thought possible, but I lost what I like to call my “soul cat”, Jack, about a month ago. He was only ten. We were inseperable and he wanted nothing more than to just always be near me. </p>
<p><img src="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/s/mt4yt5ir8ej0h3c/2015-08-01%2007.32.32.jpg" alt="Jack Jack the Attack Cat"></p>
<p>I made the choice to put him to sleep. I am so far beyond never wanting to kill something. I cried when we had to disect a worm in high school biology. Sometimes I feel like I failed him but he was dying.</p>
<p>I knew immediately that I needed to fill the hole though so I got another cat about two weeks later. So far I’m molding him into Jack 2.0 but part of me worries I’ll never be able to see him as his own cat.</p>
<p><img src="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/s/tmneusg16yo45d8/2016-02-06%2017.40.04-1.jpg" alt="Albus"></p>
<p>This is the new boy, Albus, Albie, Albinator. He’s making me happy so far.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>I don’t know what I’m doing. I think I might be burnt out but I’m not sure how to tell anymore. I just feel like I’ve stopped processing ]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[I Am Become Death]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/29/i-am-become-death/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/29/i-am-become-death/</id>
    <published>2016-03-30T03:31:10.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-03-30T03:52:21.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This post could probably also be titled: In which I type the same thing over and over again. But in less than 24 hours my body has sprung forth a vicous cold so death becomes me.</p>
<p>So I promised today that I’d test out some different markdown editors. So that’s why I’m typing the same few sentences over and over and testing out other <em>weirdness</em>.</p>
<p>My main contenders are <a href="http://macdown.uranusjr.com/" target="_blank" rel="external">MacDown</a>, <a href="http://25.io/mou/" target="_blank" rel="external">Mou</a>, and <a href="https://www.typora.io/" target="_blank" rel="external">Typora</a>. So far I’ve been writing in Typora.</p>
<p>But now I’m switching over to MacDown for the heck of it and also checking out Mou for a few words.</p>
<p>So final thoughts:</p>
<ul>
<li>MacDown and Mou are almost one and the same. I remember use Mou maybe a year ago and MacDown is the new kid on the scene.</li>
<li>Mou feels very sluggish to render the markdown output as you type. Also dat “buy meee” popup that doesn’t have a <strong>cancel</strong> only an <strong>OK</strong>. Especially on a product that was originally supposed to launch in August and we’re now in March.</li>
<li>MacDown was decent. No real drawbacks, but kinda <em>meh</em>.</li>
<li>Typora is something all together different. It doesn’t have the markdown on the left and the output on the right. <strong>It just shows you the output.</strong> It’s kinda refreshing. I could see how some people would hate it, wanting to see their exact syntax all the time, but after I’ve typed out <code>**</code> to bold a thing I don’t mind it just being <strong>bold</strong>. Especially when I can just go back and when my cursor hits the modified text it shows the syntax I used to get there.</li>
</ul>
<p>So &lt;3 to you Typora. I think you’re my new best friend except that my sick brain wants to call you ‘Tyfora’ all the time. Sorry about that.</p>
<p><img src="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/s/g3imaekpy2bixz5/Screenshot%202016-03-29%2020.49.21.png" alt="Typora word count"></p>
<p>PS. The Typora word count is a thing to behold as well.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>This post could probably also be titled: In which I type the same thing over and over again. But in less than 24 hours my body has sprung]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[What Am I Doing]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/28/what-am-i-doing/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/28/what-am-i-doing/</id>
    <published>2016-03-29T06:27:20.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-04-01T02:32:03.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’m really not sure what I’m trying to do here. I’ll style it sooner or later, but I need to start writing online again and I need it to be just my own. Leaena.com needed to become my engineering persona. I want this to be more freeform. I want to post cat pictures and writing snippets and knitting and and and…</p>
<p>So goal time:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I will write every day. At least 100 words. I can say as much or as little as I want.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Maybe I’ll list the songs I’ve listened to or talk about the weirdest link I clicked on today.</p>
<p>My fun fact today is that I learned what the hell a <a href="https://developers.google.com/protocol-buffers/" target="_blank" rel="external">Proto Buffer</a> actually is. I haven’t backend engineered in a long time. And here I said this didn’t need to be about engineering…</p>
<p>I think tomorrow I will probably talk about/test out a bunch of different markdown editors. This is <a href="http://dillinger.io/" target="_blank" rel="external">Dillinger</a> and it’s decent but I’m not sure if I want a web based solution or not. I guess it would be pretty hip of me.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>I’m really not sure what I’m trying to do here. I’ll style it sooner or later, but I need to start writing online again and I need it to ]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
