<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title><![CDATA[everything will be AMAZING]]></title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-04-01T02:24:50.200Z</updated>
  <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[lindsey]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[lindsey@clevergirl.me]]></email>
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://zespia.tw/hexo/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Cat Trills and Shadowboxing]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/30/cat-trills-and-shadowboxing/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/30/cat-trills-and-shadowboxing/</id>
    <published>2016-03-31T04:24:35.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-03-31T04:35:52.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I don’t know what I’m doing. I think I might be burnt out but I’m not sure how to tell anymore. I just feel like I’ve stopped processing basically everything around me. I’m running on autopilot. Work, home, work, home.</p>
<p>This will make me sound like even more of a crazy cat lady than was previously thought possible, but I lost what I like to call my “soul cat”, Jack, about a month ago. He was only ten. We were inseperable and he wanted nothing more than to just always be near me. </p>
<p>I made the choice to put him to sleep. I am so far beyond never wanting to kill something. I cried when we had to disect a worm in high school biology. Sometimes I feel like I failed him but he was dying.</p>
<p>I knew immediately that I needed to fill the hole though so I got another cat about two weeks later. So far I’m molding him into Jack 2.0 but part of me worries I’ll never be able to see him as his own cat.</p>
<p><img src="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/s/tmneusg16yo45d8/2016-02-06%2017.40.04-1.jpg" alt="Albus"></p>
<p>This is the new boy, Albus, Albie, Albinator. He’s making me happy so far.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>I don’t know what I’m doing. I think I might be burnt out but I’m not sure how to tell anymore. I just feel like I’ve stopped processing ]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[I Am Become Death]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/29/i-am-become-death/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/29/i-am-become-death/</id>
    <published>2016-03-30T03:31:10.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-03-30T03:52:21.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This post could probably also be titled: In which I type the same thing over and over again. But in less than 24 hours my body has sprung forth a vicous cold so death becomes me.</p>
<p>So I promised today that I’d test out some different markdown editors. So that’s why I’m typing the same few sentences over and over and testing out other <em>weirdness</em>.</p>
<p>My main contenders are <a href="http://macdown.uranusjr.com/" target="_blank" rel="external">MacDown</a>, <a href="http://25.io/mou/" target="_blank" rel="external">Mou</a>, and <a href="https://www.typora.io/" target="_blank" rel="external">Typora</a>. So far I’ve been writing in Typora.</p>
<p>But now I’m switching over to MacDown for the heck of it and also checking out Mou for a few words.</p>
<p>So final thoughts:</p>
<ul>
<li>MacDown and Mou are almost one and the same. I remember use Mou maybe a year ago and MacDown is the new kid on the scene.</li>
<li>Mou feels very sluggish to render the markdown output as you type. Also dat “buy meee” popup that doesn’t have a <strong>cancel</strong> only an <strong>OK</strong>. Especially on a product that was originally supposed to launch in August and we’re now in March.</li>
<li>MacDown was decent. No real drawbacks, but kinda <em>meh</em>.</li>
<li>Typora is something all together different. It doesn’t have the markdown on the left and the output on the right. <strong>It just shows you the output.</strong> It’s kinda refreshing. I could see how some people would hate it, wanting to see their exact syntax all the time, but after I’ve typed out <code>**</code> to bold a thing I don’t mind it just being <strong>bold</strong>. Especially when I can just go back and when my cursor hits the modified text it shows the syntax I used to get there.</li>
</ul>
<p>So &lt;3 to you Typora. I think you’re my new best friend except that my sick brain wants to call you ‘Tyfora’ all the time. Sorry about that.</p>
<p><img src="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/s/g3imaekpy2bixz5/Screenshot%202016-03-29%2020.49.21.png" alt="Typora word count"></p>
<p>PS. The Typora word count is a thing to behold as well.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>This post could probably also be titled: In which I type the same thing over and over again. But in less than 24 hours my body has sprung]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[What Am I Doing]]></title>
    <link href="http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/28/what-am-i-doing/"/>
    <id>http://everythingwillbeamazing.com/2016/03/28/what-am-i-doing/</id>
    <published>2016-03-29T06:27:20.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-03-31T04:15:35.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’m really not sure what I’m trying to do here. I’ll style it sooner or later, but I need to start writing online again and I need it to be just my own. Leaena.com needed to become my engineering persona. I want this to be more freeform. I want to post cat pictures and writing snippets and knitting and and and…</p>
<h5 id="So_goal_time:">So goal time:</h5>
<blockquote>
<p>I will write every day. At least 100 words. I can say as much or as little as I want.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Maybe I’ll ist the songs I’ve listened to or talk about the weirdest link I clicked on today.</p>
<p>My fun fact today is that I learned what the hell a <a href="https://developers.google.com/protocol-buffers/" target="_blank" rel="external">Proto Buffer</a> actually is. I haven’t backend engineered in a long time. And here I said this didn’t need to be about engineering…</p>
<p>I think tomorrow I will probably talk about/test out a bunch of different markdown editors. This is <a href="http://dillinger.io/" target="_blank" rel="external">Dillinger</a> and it’s decent but I’m not sure if I want a web based solution or not. I guess it would be pretty hip of me.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>I’m really not sure what I’m trying to do here. I’ll style it sooner or later, but I need to start writing online again and I need it to ]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
